加勒比海盗:死无对证
字幕由SSK字幕组倾情译制
字幕仅供学习，勿用于商
转载请注明出处，版权归片方所有
欢迎关注
新浪微博@SSK字幕组
SSK字幕组
父亲的诅咒
飞翔的荷兰人号
父亲
Father?
亨利 你这是干了什么
Henry, what have you done?
我说过我会找到你的
I said I'd find you.
你看看我 儿子
Look at me, son.
我不在意
I don't care.
你不该来荷兰人号
There's no place for you on the Dutchman.
他们发现你了
They know you're here.
快回家找你妈妈
Get home to your mother.
不要
No!
快走
Leave now!
否则来不及了
Before it's too late.
我不要 我不会放弃的
I won't! I'll never stop.
你就算把我扔下船 我也游回来找你
And if you throw me over, I'll come straight back.
你没看到我被这艘船诅咒了吗
Don't you see I'm cursed to this ship?
所以我才来找你
That's why I'm here.
我发现打破诅咒的方法了
I think I know a way to break your curse.
我会救你离开荷兰人号的
To free you from the Dutchman.
不要 亨利
Henry, no.
我在书上发现有一种宝物
I've read about a treasure.
它有掌控大海的神力
A treasure that holds all the power of the sea.
波赛冬的三叉戟可以打破你的诅咒
The Trident of Poseidon can break your curse.
亨利 你找不到三叉戟的
Henry, the Trident can never be found.
我连你都找到了
I found you.
那只是个传说
It's just a tale.
就像你和杰克·斯派洛的传说一样吗
Like the tales of you and Captain Jack Sparrow?
杰克会帮我找到三叉戟的
He will help me find the Trident.
你不要去找杰克
You stay away from Jack.
远离大海
Leave the sea forever.
别搞的像
You have to stop acting like...
海盗一样
A pirate?
我不会放弃的
I won't stop.
我要你回家
I want you to come home.
亨利
Henry...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
但是诅咒是无法打破的
But my curse will never be broken.
这是就是命
This is my fate.
你必须放弃
You must let me go.
我爱你 儿子
I love you, son.
杰克·斯派洛船长
Captain Jack Sparrow.
九年后
保持平稳
Keep even keel.
往背风向驶
Haul in on the lee side!
快点 你们这群船舱底的耗子
Faster, you pathetic bilge rats!
把这里的水给我抽出去
You'll pump the bilge and fill the scuppers.
我们追击的可是海盗
We're chasing down pirates!
亨利 快回来
Henry, get back here.
当心又把你赶下船
You don't wanna get kicked off another ship.
那是一艘荷兰人的船
It's a Dutch barque.
或许是海盗邦尼特强占的
Probably stolen by the Pirate Bonnet.
我的天哪
My God.
我警告过你擅自离开岗位的后果了
I warned you of leaving your post, boy.
我有话和船长说
I need to speak with the captain.
-你说什么 -让开
- What did you say? - Move!
特纳
Turner!
船要进去了 长官
She's going in, sir.
继续追
Chase her down.
不 不要追了
No, don't do it.
不要追了
Don't do it!
你哪儿来的权利命令长官 臭小子
You will not address the captain, boy.
长官 你看看航海图
Sir, look at your charts.
再往前开可就要到魔鬼三角区了
I believe you're sailing us into the Devil's Triangle.
大家听听
You hear this, men?
这小子居然还听信那老掉牙的传说
This landsman believes an old sailor's myth.
长官 无意冒犯
Sir, with all due respect,
我这辈子都在研究海上的传说
I have spent my life studying the myths of the sea.
我对每一个传说和诅咒都了如指掌
I know every legend and every curse.
我还知道开进魔鬼三角区的船
And I know ships that sail into the Triangle
有进无出
do not necessarily sail out...
我很抱歉 长官 这小子神智不清
I'm sorry, sir. This one is clearly disturbed.
长官 相信我吧 改变航向吧
Sir, trust in what I say. Change your course.
你敢对我发号施令 小子
You dare to give me orders, boy?
关起来
Arrest him!
特纳
Turner!
我不会让你害死这一船人的
I will not let you kill us all.
这是叛变
This is treason.
不
No.
-把他关起来 继续前进 -不要
- Lock him up. We're going in! - No!
把绳索系在右舷上
Belay that starboard brace.
拴紧绳索
Bind that line!
抓住锁链
Stay to the chains!
这是你最后的机会了 特纳
This was your last chance, Turner.
政府通缉令  100磅奖金
杰克 斯派洛  不论生死
要我
If it were up to me,
早就把你吊死在桅杆上了
I'd string you from the yardarm.
走吧
On deck.
快走 跟上
Hold steady, helmsman!
杰克·斯派洛
Jack Sparrow.
他早就死了
He's dead.
被埋在圣马丁岛上 连个墓碑都没有
Buried in an unmarked grave on the Isle of Saint Martin.
长官 水里有东西
Sir, there's something in the water.
右手边有条船
Ship to starboard!
那不是船 长官 是船骸
That's no ship, sir. It's a shipwreck.
不
No.
那船骸朝我们过来了
She's sailing straight toward us.
开火
Open fire!
装弹
Reload!
回防甲板
Secure the deck!
你是什么东西
What are you?
死亡
Death.
杰克·斯派洛
Jack Sparrow.
嘘
Shh!
你认识他
Do you know this pirate?
只听过名字
Only by name.
你在找他
You're looking for him?
是吗
Is that a "Yes"?
是的
Yes.
这么多年来 我们被诅咒困在魔鬼三角区
For too many years, the Triangle has cursed us...
困在这人间地狱
condemned us to this hell on Earth.
只有杰克·斯派洛
The key to our escape is Jack Sparrow...
和他的罗盘能解脱我们
and the compass which he holds.
别害怕 小子
No need to fear me, boy.
我每次都会留下一个活口替我传话
I always leave one man alive to tell the tale.
帮我找到斯派洛
Find Sparrow for me...
告诉他萨拉查船长在找他
and relay a message from Captain Salazar.
萨拉查
Salazar.
告诉他我一定会重见天日
Tell him I will behold the daylight again.
而那一天
And on that day...
就是
death...
他的忌日
death will come straight for him.
你会告诉他的对吧
Would you say that to him?
是吗
Please?
是的
Yes.
我也希望我能亲口告诉他 但是
I wish I could do it myself, but...
死人说不了话
dead men tell no tales.
加勒比海盗
死无对证
卡瑞娜·史密斯 你是恶魔之女
Carina Smyth, you're an orphan born of the devil...
你被指控使用巫术
accused of practising witchcraft.
在你死之前
Before you die...
还有什么话要说吗
do you have anything to confess?
我不是一个女巫
I confess that I'm not a witch,
我热爱科学研究
that I am a woman of science.
我自力更生
I confess that I have survived on my own...
靠着我素未谋面的父亲留下的日记
with nothing but a diary from the father I never knew...
和对我身世的探索
and a quest for the truth of who I am.
我不会放弃探索 至死方休
I confess that I will die before I give up the search.
还有我
And I confess...
说这话的时候 我已经撬开了门锁
that while we've been talking, I picked this lock.
今天 让我们庆祝圣马丁皇家银行开业
Today, we dedicate the Royal Bank of Saint Martin.
加勒比海地区最安全的银行
The most secure banking institution in the Caribbean.
新金库有五英寸厚
Our new vault is five inches thick...
重达一吨
and weighs an imperial ton.
我看到她了 我看到她了
I've got her! I've got her!
抓住她
Get her!
别让她跑了 逮住那个女巫
Don't let her get away! Stop that witch!
抓住她 她在这儿 让开让开
Stop her! She's there! Get out of the way!
让开
Get out of my way!
有了这座银行
With this bank...
圣马丁城正式步入现代世界
the town of Saint Martin enters the modern world.
-对不起 先生 -那个女巫跑了
- I'm so sorry, sir. - The witch escaped her chains.
把她抓回来 要不然你们就替她去死
Find that wicked lass, or you'll swing in her place.
是
Sir.
没有任何人 没有任何军队
No man nor an army...
可以抢走圣马丁城的财宝
can ever rob the gold from Saint Martin.
打开金库
Open the vault.
海盗
Pirate!
Pirates.
海盗
Pirate!
嗯
Hmm.
可能有点奇怪
This may seem a peculiar request...
但是你们谁能告诉我 我为什么在这儿吗
but could someone explain to me as to why I'm here?
斯科拉姆
Scrum.
还要多久
How long?
不 等等 我想起来了
No, wait, it's coming to me.
我需要清醒一下
I need just a moment to clear me head.
准备
Make ready!
就位
Present!
别开火
Hold your fire!
金库里还有个女人
There's a woman with him in the vault!
不用管那个荡妇
Never mind about that trollop.
先生 好像是你老婆
Sir, I believe that's your wife.
弗朗西丝
Frances?
我想起来了
Right, I've got it.
我想起来了 我在抢银行
I've got it! I'm robbing the bank!
-给我打死他 -噢
- Shoot him! - Ooh!
快点
Come on!
拉
Pull!
加把劲
Come on!
原计划不是这样的
That was not part of the plan.
追 别让他跑了
After him! Don't let him get away!
快点
Yo! Come on!
哦
Oh, oh!
我买了块羊肉 是吧
Well, I got this mutton, didn't I?
羊肉可贵了
Oh, that was too expensive.
狗和女人不得入内
还从没有女人碰过我的大镜镜
No woman's ever handled my Herschel.
让开
Clear a path!
不不不
Oh, no, no, no!
停下 停下 停下
Stop! Stop! Stop!
进去
Get inside!
右转
Hard to starboard.
先生
Sir.
你的天文定向不准
Your celestial fix was off.
我向北调了两度
I've adjusted two degrees North.
你的星图不会再有偏差了
Your map will no longer be imprecise.
虽然你得重新画了
Although you will have to start again with it.
你是个女巫
You're a witch.
不 我不是
No, I'm not.
我可是绘制了两百多颗恒星的星图的女科学家
Am I a witch for having catalogued over 200 stars?
女巫
Witch!
血月要来了
There is a blood moon coming.
我需要买一个航行表
I simply need to purchase a chronometer.
你要肯卖 我付你双倍价格
I'll pay you double for selling to a woman.
来人
Help!
有个女巫在我店里
There's a witch in my shop!
来人
Help!
来人啊 有个女巫在我店里
Help! There's a witch in my shop!
还有一个海盗 有个女巫还有个海盗在我店里
And a pirate! There's a witch and a pirate in my shop!
哇 那今天真是你的幸运日
Well, it's your lucky day!
你们看到我的银行了吗
Have either of the four of you seen my bank?
找到了
Found it!
这是计划的一部分吗
Were you part of the plan?
我不想找麻烦
I'm not looking for trouble.
这条路挑得可真好啊
What a horrible way to live.
抓住那个女巫 抓住她
Stop that witch! Get her!
没路了 怎么办
We're trapped. What do we do?
对 她就在那儿 快点儿
Yeah, there she is! Quickly!
快尖叫
You need to scream.
那边 抓住那个女人
Over there! Secure that woman!
你这个下流的海盗
You filthy pirate!
别骂人啊
No need for name-calling!
快点儿 小伙子们
Come on, lads!
杰克
Jack!
嗯
Huh?
桥
Bridge?
是空的
It's empty!
钱呢
Where is the dosh?
你觉得抢个金库很容易吗
Do you think that robbing a bank is easy?
首先 你们这帮胆小的崽子们竟敢
You gaggle of gutless heels of the womb's guilty...
把我弄得那么狼狈
of putting me in this dreadful pickle in the first place.
现在排队给我上交你们的战利品
Now line up and offer me your tribute.
你想要我们给你钱吗
You want us to pay you?
我难道不是这船的船长吗
Am I not the captain of this ship?
你管这叫船吗
You call this a ship?
宝藏在哪里
Where's the treasure?
我们都快饿死了
All of us are starving.
我们不会再跟着一个没有船的船长了
We will no longer follow a captain without a ship.
我有船
I have a ship.
黑珍珠号从未离开我
Black Pearl has never left me side.
海盗巴博萨现在统治着这片海域
The pirate Barbossa rules these seas now.
他有十条船 满载火炮
Has 10 ships, guns full.
更不用说他的加农炮了
Not to mention his cannonballs.
听说每个十八磅呢
18 pounds each they say.
一条腿的男人有个十八磅的“炮弹”吗
One-legged man with 18 pound balls?
怪不得他走路那么滑稽
That's why he walks funny.
噢 好了好了 伙伴们
Oh, come, come, mates.
我们之前不是一起找到了马其顿宝藏吗
Did we not find the Treasure of Macedonia together?
那就是一堆腐烂的木头
It was a troll of rotten wood.
-还有弥达斯王的金子 -一堆驴粪
- Gold of King Midas. - Pile of donkey dung.
面对现实吧 杰克
Face it, Jack.
你衰神附体了
Bad luck dogs you day and night.
别胡扯
Now that is a blatant fabrication.
你好运到头了
You've lost your luck.
你失去了船
You've lost your ship.
现在 你将失去你的船员
Now, you've lost your crew.
杰克·斯派洛不再是我们的船长了
Jack Sparrow is no longer our captain.
抱歉了 杰克
I'm sorry, Jack.
但是我们缘分已尽
But we've reached the end of the horizon.
很好
Right then.
你们都被解雇了 喂
You're all dismissed. Eh?
你们所有人 被解雇了
All of ya, dismissed.
听着 你们再也不能跟随杰克船长
You'll never sail with Captain Jack Sparrow again,
出海了
tell you that.
全城都在讨论你
The whole town speaks of you.
君主号唯一的幸存者
The only survivor of the Monarch.
抱着一块浮木
A boy who paddled all the way to Saint Martin
一直漂到了圣马丁的男孩儿
against the tide on a piece of driftwood.
被发现的时候胡言乱语着海盗和三叉戟
Found jabbering about pirates and tridents.
拜托 长官 放我走
Please, sir, let me go of these chains.
我的职责是保护这座岛屿和这片水域
My job is to protect this island and these waters.
而且你的袖子被撕开了
And your sleeves have been ripped.
是叛徒的标记
The mark of treason.
我们被袭击了 被死去的
We were attacked by the dead...
你是个逃兵 懦夫
You're a coward who ran from battle.
等着判死刑吧你
And that is how you'll die.
我相信你不是个懦夫
I don't believe you're a coward.
请离我远点儿 护士
Please leave me, sister.
我冒着生命危险来见你
I've risked my life to come here,
是为了看看那些传闻是不是真的
to see if the rumours are true.
你知道三叉戟
You speak of the Trident?
你是谁
Who are you?
告诉我你为什么要找三叉戟
Tell me why you seek the Trident.
三叉戟可以破除海上的任何诅咒
The Trident can break any curse at sea.
我父亲被一个诅咒困住了
My father is trapped by such a curse.
你知道从科学的角度看 诅咒什么的故事都是假的
You're aware that curses are not supported by science.
世上也没有鬼
Neither are ghosts.
所以你走火入魔了吗 我就不应该来到这里
So you have gone mad? I should never have come here.
那你为什么来
Then why did you come here?
因为我要离开这座岛
Because I need to get off this island.
-去解开没人能 -能读懂的地图
- To solve The Map No Man... - No Man Can Read.
波塞冬的地图
Left by Poseidon himself.
你认识古文
You've read the ancient text?
那古籍被翻译成了各种语言
In each language they were written.
但是这个地图没人见过 号称天书 没人能看懂
But this map has never been seen nor read by any man.
正好 我可是仙女下凡
Luckily, I'm a woman.
这是伽利略的日记
This is the diary of Galileo Galilei.
他一生都在搜寻三叉戟
He spent his life searching for the Trident.
所以他发明了望远镜
It's why he invented the spyglass...
这也是天文学家们
why astronomers have spent their lives
仰望星空的原因
staring into the sky.
所以你是说 天书地图的秘密
So you're saying The Map No Man Can Read
藏在星星中吗
is hidden in the stars?
这是我父亲留给我的
It was left to me by my father.
他相信我能够找到没人能找到的东西
He believed I could find what no man has ever found
我不会让他失望的
and I will not let him down.
血月就快出现了
Soon there will be a blood moon.
只有那时才能根据地图
Only then can the map be read.
找到三叉戟
And the Trident found.
你是谁
Who are you?
卡瑞纳·史密斯
Carina Smyth.
如果你想要救你的父亲
If you wish to save your father,
你得来救我
you'll have to save me.
去找艘船 我们会一起找到三叉戟
Find us a ship and the Trident will be ours.
别跑 女巫
Turn to me, witch.
站住
Hold.
他不见了
He's gone!
他不见了 长官
He's gone, sir!
找到那个懦夫
Find that coward.
把他和这个女巫一起吊死
He'll hang with the witch.
行动
Move out!
你们以为杰克船长一贫如洗了吗 嗯
Think Captain Jack's washed up, eh?
我好多年没洗过澡了
I've not had a wash in years.
搜查那边的小巷子
Check the alley down there.
你们俩 去搜查教堂 剩下的跟着我
You two, check the church. The rest of you, with me.
倒霉
Bugger.
能给我杯酒吗 拜托
May I please have a drink, please?
给我银子
Show me your silver.
银子
Silver?
我们做个交易怎么样
How about a trade?
给我酒
Give me the bottle.
船长 发生什么了
Capitán, what's happening?
是杰克
Jack Sparrow.
杰克抛弃了他的罗盘
Jack Sparrow has given away the compass.
阳光 是阳光
Daylight. Daylight.
我们自由了
We are free!
现在 是时候去抓个海盗了
Now, now. It's time to hunt a pirate.
取海盗的命
Pirate's life.
来爸比这儿 噢
Come to daddy. Oh!
这就是我们在找的人
Just the man we've been looking for.
为什么 为什么要找我
Why? Why am I looked for?
海盗 杰克船长
Let it be known that the pirate, Jack Sparrow,
将在黎明被处决
will be executed at dawn.
处决
Executed?
我不会再踏入这个镇子了 长官
I will never set foot in this town again, sir.
记住我的话
You mark my words.
去死吧 你这个狗杂种
Dead now, you cur.
我是认真的 你知道
I do mean it, you know.
我不会再回来了
I shall never be back here again.
嗯
Huh.
“要释放大海的力量
"To release the power of the sea...
必须分离一切”
"All must divide."
是个岛
It's an island.
星星指向了一座岛
The stars lead to an island.
看这 长官
Look right here, sir.
很好 把剩下的带去牢房
Very good. Take the rest to the cells.
我在找一个海盗 杰克船长
I'm looking for a pirate. Jack Sparrow.
滚开
Bugger off.
喂 我有话和你说
Psst. I need to speak with you.
把你的剑给我
Hand me your sword.
我没有剑
I don't have a sword.
什么样的士兵会没有武器呢
What kind of soldier has no weapon?
我就是那个犯叛国罪被通缉的
I'm currently wanted for treason.
看来不是什么好人啊
So not the very good kind then.
我在找一个海盗 杰克船长
I'm looking for a pirate. Captain Jack Sparrow.
好吧 今天是你的幸运日
Well, today is your lucky day.
因为我就是杰克船长
'Cause I just happen to be Captain Jack Sparrow.
不 不可能
No, it can't be.
我多年来就为了寻找 你这样子的人吗
I've spent years searching for... this?
伟大的杰克船长不是牢房中的酒鬼
The great Jack Sparrow is not some drunk in a cell.
你有船吗 有船员吗
Do you even have a ship? A crew?
裤子呢
Pants?
一个伟大的海盗不需要这些乱七八糟的东西
A great pirate does not require such intricacies.
你知道我等这一刻等了多久吗
Do you know how long I've been waiting for this moment?
我为了来这儿冒了多少险
The risks I've taken to be here.
你确定你就是杰克船长吗
Are you sure you're the Jack Sparrow?
真正该问的是 你是谁
Real question is, who are you?
我叫亨利·特纳
My name is Henry Turner.
是威尔·特纳和伊丽莎白·斯旺的儿子
Son of Will Turner and Elizabeth Swann.
呃
Ugh!
你是他们俩的邪恶产物啊
You're the evil spawn of them two?
你妈咪提起过我吗
Does mommy ever ask about me?
没有
No.
噢那么
Oh, go on.
她在睡梦中叫过我的名字吗
She call my name in her sleep?
她从没提过你
She never spoke of you.
你确定我们俩说的是一个人吗
Are you sure we're talking about the same people?
你爹被诅咒了
He's a cursed eunuch.
你娘有一头金发 固执 爱撅嘴
She's golden-haired, stubborn, pouty lips.
脖子像长颈鹿 还有两个完美的
Neck like a giraffe. And two of those wonderful...
是的 是她
Yes! Yes, it's her.
我要你听我说 杰克
I need you to listen, Jack,
因为这一刻我只有你了
because at the moment you're all I've got.
我找到了一个救我父亲的方法
I found a way to save my father.
有一样东西可以破除他的诅咒
There is one thing that can break his curse
把他从飞翔的荷兰人中解放出来
and free him from the Dutchman.
波塞冬的三叉戟
The Trident of Poseidon.
嗯
Ah.
通过号称天书的地图寻找的宝藏
The treasure to be found with The Map That No Man Can Read.
我没听说过
Never heard of it.
这座监狱里有个女孩儿 杰克
There is a girl inside this prison, Jack,
她拿着那张地图
who holds that map.
当月亮变成血红色 就能找到三叉戟
The moon has turned to blood, the Trident will be found...
你可以成为海上领主
and you could be the one who holds the sea...
重现往日雄风
and with it become all that you once were.
伟大的
The great...
杰克
Jack!
抱歉 我们还没完事儿吗
I'm so sorry. Were you still talking?
我可能打了个盹
I believe I nodded off a bit.
还有一件事
One more thing.
有个叫萨拉查的
A message from someone you know,
给你带了个口信儿
named Captain Salazar.
我好像是认识个名字是西班牙语
I once knew a Spaniard named...
的西班牙人
something in Spanish.
海上屠夫
The Butcher of the Sea.
他吗 不 不
Him? No, no.
他早死了 死的透透的
Quite happily, he's dead. Very, very dead.
-船沉了 -在魔鬼三角
- Ship went down. - Inside the Triangle.
他来追杀你了 杰克
He's coming for you, Jack,
就像传说中所讲的那样找你复仇
to seek revenge as the dead man's tale is told.
我才不信你
I don't believe you.
他说什么了
What did he say?
他说你的罗盘是他逃脱的关键
He said your compass was the key to his escape.
他带着一船死人来追杀你了 杰克
An army of dead are coming straight for you, Jack.
波塞顿的三叉戟是你唯一的希望
The Trident of Poseidon is your only hope.
我们达成共识了吗
Do we have an accord?
我才不去告诉他
Well, I'm not going in there to tell him.
明明是你的鬼主意
It was your idea.
不 我的主意由你来告诉他
No, it was my idea for you to tell him.
相比我他更喜欢你
He likes you more than me.
他谁都不喜欢
He doesn't like anybody.
抱歉 老大
Sorry, sir.
我们知道你说永远不能打扰你
We know you said never to disturb you.
不能一来就是坏消息
Or to come in without good cause.
并且要事先通报
Or to speak without first, um...
所以我们想问下
Asking ourselves...
我们现在有个事您看是当讲不当讲
Whether our thoughts were absolutely necessary.
就像那次船着火了
Like the time the ship was on fire.
就是个应当报告的事
That being an example of necessary thought.
再次道歉 我们引起了那次火灾
Sir, again, we do apologise for starting that fire.
有屁快放
Speak.
是您的船出事了
It's your ships, sir.
而且敌人没有掠夺财宝
They're being attacked by an enemy that takes no riches.
毫无理由
Kills without provocation.
我的船
My ships?
不可能
Not possible.
已经有三只沉了 老大
Three have already been sunk, sir.
据说是被一个叫萨拉曼的的穿着击沉的
They've been sunk by a captain called Salamander.
萨默瓦
Samovar.
是萨拉查
Salazar.
就是这个 老大
That's it, your sirness.
每袭击条船都他会留一个活口来传信儿
He leaves one man from each vessel to tell the tale.
整条船都沉了
The entire fleet is being sunk...
马上就轮到我们了
and we'll soon be dead.
估计要失业了
And quite possibly out of business.
我需要和你们的女巫独处一会
I'll be needing some time with your witch.
恭候多时了 船长
I've been expecting you, Captain.
您要来点茶吗
Perhaps you'd like some tea?
我就算了 谢谢你的好意
I shall pass. Thank ye kindly.
进我的门的代价是鲜血 船长
The price of crossing my door is blood, Captain.
也许这就是门可罗雀的原因
That explains why you're not so busy.
每个人最后都会付出代价的
Everyone pays eventually.
山萨 你我有多年交情
Shansa, you and I made a bond long ago.
我把你从绞刑架救下 还记得吗
I saved you from the gallows, remember?
为此我帮你诅咒了你的敌人
And I cursed your enemies.
现在你满怀恐惧来向我求助
But now you come to me in fear,
死亡已经笼罩了海洋
as the dead have taken command of the sea.
他们想从我身上得到什么
And what would the dead be wanting with me?
不是你 船长
Not you, Captain.
它们在寻找一只麻雀
They're searching for a Sparrow.
杰克吗
Jack?
杰克会和一个姑娘和小伙
Jack will sail for the Trident...
一起寻找三叉戟
with a girl and a Pearl.
三叉戟无可寻之处
The Trident can never be found.
三叉戟是杰克唯一的希望
The Trident is Jack's only hope.
死人已经控制了海上
The dead are conquering the sea,
但他们无法踏上陆地
unable to step on dry land.
也许你该告老还乡
Maybe you should retire to the countryside.
你说回村里 种地吗
You mean grass? On a farm?
当他们吞掉我的财富 我却在挤奶 做起司吗
Milkin' a cow, makin' cheese, while they sink my treasure?
船长 问问你自己
Ask yourself this, Captain.
那些财富值得你牺牲吗
Is this a treasure worth dying for?
我是一个海盗
I'm a pirate.
生死如一
Always will be.
我该如何拯救我的财富
So how do I save what be mine?
杰克有一只罗盘
Jack held a compass
会帮你找到你最渴望的东西
which points you to the thing you desire most.
但抛弃罗盘
But betray the compass,
它就会释放你最大的恐惧
and it releases your greatest fear.
一个海盗最大的恐惧是萨拉查 对吗
A pirate's greatest fear be Salazar, is it?
你怎么拿到的
How did you get this?
我有我的门路
I have my ways.
在杰克找到三叉戟之前把死人引向他
Lead them to Jack before he finds the Trident...
你所有的财富都会物归原主
and all your treasure will come back to you.
是时候和死人做笔交易了
Time to make a deal with the dead.
快点 海盗
Come on, pirate!
稍等
Hold on. Stop!
老爹
Dad?
老杰克
Uncle Jack!
小杰克 最近怎么样呀
Jackie boy! How's it going?
没什么差 你呢
Can't complain really. You?
一上午都在等被打
I've been waitin' all morning in here for a beating.
但没人敢来
But the service is terrible.
真可耻
Shameful.
杰克
Jack.
大海已经被鲜血染红
The oceans have turned to blood.
呆在陆地上最安全
Best to stay on dry land where it's safe.
我就要在陆地上被处死了
I'm about to be executed on dry land.
有道理
Good point.
我跟你讲过骷髅的笑话吗
Did I ever tell you the one about the skeleton?
当然 讲过很多次了
Yes, you have. Many times, in fact.
骷髅走进一间酒吧
Skeleton goes into a bar...
点了一杯啤酒和一根拖把
orders a beer and a mop.
一如既往好笑
Funny as ever.
赶紧走吧
Come on, let's go.
如果他们要开膛 一定要找维克托
Oh, if they disembowel you, ask for Victor.
他下手最温柔
He's got the softest hands.
-多谢 -而且提我的名字
- Thank you! - And mention my name.
可以免去被砍脚
They won't cut your feet off.
赶紧 你第一个
Come on. You're up first.
你想怎么死啊海盗
And how would you like to die, pirate?
绞死 枪决
Hanging, firing squad,
或者试试新发明 断头台
or a new invention: the guillotine.
断头台 有点法国味儿
Guillotine? Sounds French.
我喜欢法国的
I love the French.
你知道是他们发明了蛋黄酱吗
Did you know that they invented mayonnaise?
能有多糟 法国人那点本事
How bad could it be? It's French, eh?
我去
Oh, well, then.
我改变主意了
I've changed me mind!
天呢 饶了我吧
No, please! Have mercy upon me!
我还尿床呢
I'm a bed-wetter.
见鬼
Oh, come on.
我还得自己走上来送死啊
I mean, I have to walk upstairs as well for this?
拿篮子来
Bring the basket.
篮子 什么鬼
Basket? Why?
绑起来
Strap him down!
提议一下
Here's an idea. Here's an idea.
为什么不试试老式的石刑呢
Why don't we try a good old-fashioned stoning, eh?
我现在特别想被石头砸死
I'd kill to be stoned right now.
大家都能参与多好玩
Gets the crowd involved, doesn't it?
我要跟开膛的维克托讲话
I should like to speak to Victor in Disembowelment.
我要跟
I should like to speak to...
我不是个爱抱怨的人
I'm not one to complain normally,
但这篮子里的头有点多吧
but this basket's full of heads.
克瑞娜·史密斯的遗言
The final words of Carina Smyth.
安静
Quiet!
克瑞娜·史密斯的遗言
The final words of Carina Smyth.
尊敬的阁下们 我不是女巫
Good sirs, I'm not a witch...
但我原谅你们的愚蠢
but I forgive your common dimwittedness
和空洞的头脑
and feeble brains.
总之 你们的智商和山羊差不多
In short, most of you have the mind of a goat.
抱歉 阁下
Pardon me, sir.
难道临死的人
Is it not common practice for those about to be executed...
都会被允许 怎么说 发牢骚吗
to be granted a last, I don't know, something...
要是你耐心点
I believe I was making a point.
就知道我讲的有道理
If you could just be patient.
才不
No!
我的脑袋马上就要落地了 十万火急
My head's about to be lopped off, hence the urgency.
人家的脖子还马上要断了呢
And my neck is to be broken.
你知道吗 实际上
Did you know that on occasion,
绞刑不会真的弄断脖子
the neck doesn't actually break?
只是有点疼
It just hurts.
-什么鬼 -确实如此
- What? -  Oh, yes.
我见过被吊了几个小时的人
I've seen men swing for hours,
眼睛鼓起 舌头吐在外面
eyes bulging, tongues swelling...
-还发出恶心的汩汩声 -我能说完吗
- revolting gurgling sound. - May I finish?
不能 你很幸运
No! You're lucky.
我也想被吊死
Wish I was hung.
-先砍了那个海盗 我可以等会儿 -但是女巫优先
- Kill the filthy pirate. I'll wait. - But witches first.
我才不是女巫 你没听我说话吗
I'm not a witch. Were you not listening?
听你这个像
Quite hard to listen
山羊一样蠢的人讲话很难
when you have the mind of a goat.
够了 两个都杀了
Enough! Kill them both!
再拿个绳套
Get another noose!
你真的觉得你能打败我们吗 小鬼
Did you think you could defeat us, boy?
没有 阁下
No, sir.
我只是来转移注意力的
I'm just the diversion.
开火
Fire!
还是被石头砸死比较好
Still rather be stoned!
装弹
Reload!
呃
Ugh!
谢谢
Thank you.
受死吧
Die!
-过来 你这个混蛋海盗 -嘿
- Come here, you pirate scum! - Hey, hey!
不
Oh, no.
你想干嘛 不 不 不
What are you doing? No, no, no!
小心点
Careful!
马
Horses?
噢
Oh!
谢谢
Thank you!
不用客气 小姐
You're welcome, me lady.
抓到你了
Got you!
就知道你们这群叛徒会回来
Knew you'd come crawling back, traitor.
那个姓特纳的给了我们十块碎银
The Turner boy gave us 10 silver pieces
保你的脑袋
to save your neck.
从此我们就是同盟了
From this moment on, we are to be allies.
考虑到你左手现在的位置
Considering where your left hand is,
我觉得我们的关系不止于此
I'd say we're more than that.
我们会一起找到三叉戟 一言为定
We find the Trident together. Do I have your word?
除了我的承诺你什么都有
You're holding everything but my word.
你给我一笔钱吧
Then I bestow upon you the honour of saving me
作为救我的回报
for a small donation.
你指望我们救了你还给你钱吗
You expect us to pay you to save you?
对呀
Yes.
只要十个银元
For a mere 10 pieces.
疯子
Madness!
我们最多付你五个
We won't pay more than five!
那好吧 就八个吧
Well, then... Eight it is.
也许我们可以一会再谈这个
Perhaps we could discuss this later
因为我正尽力抬着你的左舷
as I'm having trouble hoisting your port!
你离我的左舷远着呢 这是我的船尾
You are far from port. That is my stern.
你确定
Are you sure?
非常确定
Positive.
瞧瞧
Well, look at this.
我要是杀死了懦夫 女巫也会被吊死
If I kill the coward, the witch hangs.
一箭双雕呀
Two for the price of one.
别放开我
Please don't let go of me.
他真杀了我要不放就难了
Might be difficult once he kills me.
先生们 就是这两个阶下囚会带着我们找到三叉戟
Gentlemen, these two prisoners will lead us to the Trident.
船长
Captain.
你真的觉得我们能找到三叉戟吗
Do you really think we can find the Trident?
吉布斯大副 别婆婆妈妈的
Master Gibbs, you old worrywart,
这件事从头到尾都没有需要担心的地方
there's nothing to be concerned about at all.
你觉得有什么不妥吗
What could possibly go wrong, eh?
这就是你的方案吗
So this was your plan?
被海盗折磨致死
To be tortured and killed by pirates.
你说过你需要一艘船
You said you needed a ship.
这个也能叫船
You call this a ship?
放下碎石
Cut the shard!
准备入水
Prepare to drown!
我亲爱的小心肝船员们 终于 今天
Me dear beloved crew, finally, today is...
好像有点不对劲
Something's gone wrong.
她浮起来啦
She floats!
向前直行
Ship dead ahead!
先生
Sir.
我们永远不会质疑您作为一个船长的选择
We would never question your reason as a captain but...
但是您能解释一下
But is there a reason...
作为一个船长 你为什么要让船
as captain, you've chosen to sail
向着这么不合理的一个方向航行吗
in this unreasonable direction?
让男人们准备好到甲板上来
Tell the men to prepare to be boarded...
站在这里表现出一个男人该有的样子
to stand their ground and show no fear.
船长 一艘船正朝着我们驶来
Capitán, a ship sails toward us.
萨拉扎船长
Capitán Salazar...
我听说您在寻找杰克·斯派咯
I hear you be looking for Jack Sparrow.
停止攻击
Hold point!
等待指示
And await orders.
我是巴博萨船长
My name is Captain Barbossa,
此刻我充满诚意的站在您面前
and I stand before you with cordial intent.
诚意
Cordial intent.
你们听见了吗
Do you hear that?
这个海盗想显示他的诚意
This pirate wishes to be cordial.
看看我是如何展示诚意的吧
So let me show you what my cordiality is, hombre.
我的剑每敲击一下地面 你就会失去一个船员
Every time I tap my sword, one of your men will die.
所以我建议你说快一点
So I suggest that you speak quickly.
你想看我敲得快一点吗 船长
Might want to go a bit faster, Capitán.
杰克·斯派咯在哪
Where's Jack Sparrow?
杰克去寻找三叉戟了
Jack be sailing for the Trident.
不 海洋已经是我们的地盘了
No, the sea belongs to the dead.
三叉戟掌控着海洋
The Trident controls the sea.
不 不
No! No!
没有什么宝物
There's no treasure.
没有什么宝物可以救他
There's no treasure that can save him.
他将会死去 而你也一样
He will die, as will you.
我是唯一一个可以带你找到他的人
I be the only one that can lead you to him.
我保证你会得到杰克的小命
I declare you shall have Jack's life
在明天日出之前
by sunrise on the morrow...
到时候再杀我也不迟
or you can take me own then.
成交吗
Do we have an accord?
带我去找他
Take me to him,
你就可以活下去讲述这个传说
and you will live to tell the tale.
一言为定
You have my word.
代表我的船员们感谢您
I thank ye on behalf of me crew.
你可以带着剩下的船员
Well, hey, you can take what's left of them.
还活着的人到船上来
The living come aboard!
濒死海鸥号
好吧 先生们
Right, gentlemen.
卡瑞娜 我们时间不多了
Carina, we haven't got much time.
死人正在追我们
The dead are sailing straight for us.
真的吗
Is that so?
真的 我和他们对话过
Yes, I've spoken to them.
和他们对话
You've spoken to them?
那你也和海怪和美人鱼说过话喽
Have you spoken to krakens and mermaids as well?
海怪不会说话 人人都知道
Krakens don't speak. Everyone knows that.
当然 我就不应该救你
Of course. I never should have saved you.
昨晚 出现了血月
Last night, there was a blood moon,
就像你描述的那样
just as you described.
告诉我那意味着什么
Tell me what it revealed.
那我又为什么要相信你呢
And why should I trust you?
我托住你的左舷的时候你是相信我的 记得吗
You trusted me to hold your port, remember?
那是我的船尾 看来你很需要在海上多生活段时间
It was my stern. Clearly, you need to spend more time at sea.
告诉我你的发现 我发誓一定会帮你
Tell me what you found and I promise to help you.
我不需要帮助
I don't need any help.
那你为什么来找我呢 卡瑞娜
Then why did you come to me, Carina?
为什么我们两人会被一起这样绑在大海中央
Why are we tied together in the middle of the sea,
去寻找同一个宝藏
chasing the same treasure?
月亮揭示了一个线索
The moon revealed a clue.
“要释放海洋力量 必须分离一切”
"To release the power of the sea, all must divide."
分离 那是什么意思
Divide? What does it mean?
我还不确定
I'm not sure yet.
那我们一起来搞清楚
Then we'll find out.
这地图啥也没有啊
There is no map in this map.
把我的日记给我
Give me my diary.
把天书地图给我
Give me The Map No Man Can Read.
如果你能读懂
If you could read it,
它就不会叫“号称天书的地图”了
then it wouldn't be called "The Map No Man Can Read."
求你了 别和她起争执
I beg you, please, don't argue with her.
这艘船上绝大部分人都不认字
Most of the men on this ship can't read.
所以所有的地图都可以叫“号称天书的地图”
Which makes all maps The Maps That No Man Can Read.
如果你们都不懂 那我们拿着它也没用
Well, if you can't read it, then you have no use for it or me.
我再说一遍
Let me start again.
告诉我怎么读地图
Show me the map.
做不到 地图现在还没有出现
I can't. It doesn't yet exist.
她是个女巫
She's a witch!
我是天文学家
I'm an astronomer.
哦 她是养驴的
Ah! Ah, she breeds donkeys.
什么 不是 天文学家是解读天象的人
What? No. An astronomer contemplates the sky.
-骑在驴子上吗 -不 跟驴没关系
- Yeah, on a donkey? - No! There's no donkey!
那你怎么喂驴呢
Well, then how do you breed them?
让我再简单地复述一遍问题
Allow me to simplify this equation.
告诉我怎么看懂地图...
Give me the map...
要不我就杀了...
or I will kill...
他 我就杀了他
him. I'll kill him.
杀吧
Go on then.
你就是在吓唬人
You're bluffing.
但你可脸红了
And you're blushing.
扔到海里去
Throw him over.
来吧 来吧
Come. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
这个叫船底拖人
We call this keelhauling.
年轻的亨利就要被扔进...
Young Henry will be tossed over...
然后在船底下被船拽着
and he will be dragged under the ship.
挺好 你们还等什么呢
All right. What're you waiting for?
他看起来不是...
Uh, he doesn't appear to be...
-堵上 堵上 -不 我可不是在唬人
- Zip, zip. - Nope, not bluffing, me.
他想说什么
He's trying to say something.
不 船上没有食物了 不好意思
No, no, we don't have any food aboard. Sorry.
要是幸运的话 他在被藤壶割成碎片以前
If he's lucky, he'll drown before the barnacles
就会淹死
shred him to ribbons.
藤壶
Barnacles?
就感觉像有上万把小刀在割你的背
Like a thousand knives across your back.
而且因为鲜血会引来鲨鱼
'Course the blood attracts sharks.
鲨鱼
Sharks?
船头有鲨鱼
Shark off the bow!
我想这下他游得再快也没用了
I would say that swimming is no longer his primary concern.
地图在这儿
The map is there!
在哪
Where?
你的手指尖上吗
On the tip of your finger?
不 在天上
No. In the heavens.
日记会指引我发现隐藏在星群中的地图
That diary will lead me to a map hidden in the stars.
把他捞上来 今晚我就能找出地图
Let him up. I'll find it tonight.
对不起 我捞不上来他 你自己看看吧
Sorry, can't bring him up. Look for yourself.
就像我刚说的...你脸红了
As I said... blushing.
可恶的海盗
Filthy pirate.
海水被鲜血染红
The sea has turned to blood.
一个被冲上岸的水手说到了三叉戟
A sailor washed ashore talking about the Trident.
他在找杰克·斯派罗
He was looking for Jack Sparrow.
就是那个从绞刑架上救下了一根女巫的海盗
The same pirate who saved a witch from the gallows.
她不是女巫
She's no witch.
但你是
But you are.
而你会帮助我们
And you're going to help us.
你在害怕 中尉
You're afraid, Lieutenant.
船只在夜间起火
As ships burn in the night,
你想知道能不能保住自己的船
you want to know if you can save your own.
如果三叉戟真的存在
If the Trident is real.
告诉我墙上写了些什么否则你也会死
You're going to read that wall for me or you will die.
英国皇室会找到三叉戟并掌控海洋
The British Empire will have the Trident and rule the sea.
我想知道海盗带着那个女巫
I want to know where that pirate is going
朝哪去了
with that witch.
你的命运藏在这些星图中
Your destiny is in these stars.
我会为你指明航向
I will set your course.
有妖怪
Spaghetti wolf!
我为什么要费劲来找你呢
Why did I bother coming to you?
死人在追杀我们而你却无所事事
The dead are hunting us down and you do nothing.
无所事事 我这叫无所事事吗
Nothing! You call this nothing?
你就是喝醉了 在睡觉
You're drunk! And you're sleeping.
没错呀 我可是同时在做两件事
My point exactly! I am doing two things at once.
对改变不了的事我们也没办法 伙计
You can't save the unsaveable, mate.
不管你想还是不想 杰克 你必须要帮我
Like it or not, Jack, you're going to help me.
我一定要解除父亲身上的咒语
I will break my father's curse.
下次拿起武器之前 孩子 先确定自己有没有胜算
Next time you raise a sword, boy, be the last to die.
哦
Oh.
我应该建议你多跟她调调情吗
Might I suggest you entice her with a bit of flattery?
我是为了我父亲而来 不会想别的
I'm here for my father, nothing more.
我就知道 你已经为了她神魂颠倒了
I knew it. Absolutely smitten with her.
给你个建议 在追一个肤色偏黑的女孩的时候
Now, a bit of discretion when courting a brunette...
千万不要也追她姐姐
never pursue her sister.
但是如果你抵抗不了她姐姐的魅力
But if you cannot avoid the charm of her sister...
只能杀了她的兄弟
kill the brother.
懂了吗
Savvy?
不 我不懂
No, I do not savvy.
生什么气呀
Who hurt you?
对了 为了这个有用的小建议
By the way, that little sliver of knowledge
你应该付我五个银元
will cost you five pieces.
我不会为了这个给你钱
I'm not paying you for that.
永远别对女人说这样的话
Never say that to a woman.
有些事情你看不到
Just because you can't see something,
不代表它不存在
doesn't mean it's not there.
就像地图
Like the map?
我必须找出地图
I have to find it.
只有它能让我找到我究竟是谁
It's the only link to who I am.
我的父亲又是谁
Who my father was.
所以我们都是在寻找自己的父亲
So we've both spent our lives searching for our fathers.
也许我们之间的距离比你想的更近
Perhaps you and I are closer than you think.
太阳在升起 你的时间也快到了
The sun is up, and so is your time.
我不是要反驳你
Not to disagree,
只是我们约定的时间可是日出结束时
but the precision of our accord ends at sunrise.
这只不过才刚开始日出 太阳还未完全升起
This be but first light, far from a fully risin' sun.
而我知道你是个重荣誉讲信誉的人
And I know you to be a man of honour.
信誉吗 你一点都不了解我
Honour? You know nothing of me.
我知道被杰克·斯派洛戏耍的感受
I know what it's like to be bested by Jack Sparrow.
他是我们共同的敌人
He's an enemy to us...
你根本不知道我是谁
You don't know who I am.
我听说过关于一个强大的西班牙船长的故事
I've heard stories of a mighty Spanish captain,
他号称海上屠夫
El Matador Del Mar.
一个在海上肆虐
A man who scourged the sea,
猎杀了成千上万人的男人
hunted and killed thousands of men.
不 不 不 男人 不 不 不
No, no, no. Men, no. No, no, no.
呃 海盗吗
Pirates, eh?
海盗啊
Pirates.
海盗已经感染了大海一代又一代
Pirates had infected the seas for generations.
在很早以前海盗就夺走了我父亲和我祖父的性命
Taking the life of my father and his father before.
所以我立誓要将这瘟疫铲除 永绝后患
So I vowed to end this plague once and for all.
这才是我做的一切 我摧毁了数十艘海盗船
And that is what I did. I destroyed dozens of ships.
剩下的船只聚集在一起 试图击败我
The last ones joined together to try and defeat me!
可他们很快就意识到希望渺茫
But they soon realised it was hopeless.
寂静玛丽号是所向披靡 无人可挡的
Nothing could stop the Silent Mary.
攻击水线下方
Hit them below the water line.
加紧火力 加紧火力
Vamos! Vamos!
坚持住 小伙子们
Hang on, boys!
大海终于恢复纯净
The sea was finally pure.
他们肮脏的旗帜终于不能再玷污圣洁的大海了
Their wretched flags would no longer stain the sea.
他们开始向我乞求怜悯
They are begging for mercy.
怜悯 你们想要怜悯吗
CAPTAIN SALAZAR: Mercy? Mercy?
对你们 无需怜悯
There's no mercy.
准备好
LIEUTENANT LESARO: Make ready!
求求你们 救救我们吧
Please, help us!
再见
CAPTAIN SALAZAR: Adi贸s!
开火
Fire!
只能靠你了 杰克
It's up to you now, Jack.
这罗盘会指向你此刻最渴望的东西
This compass points towards what you want most.
永远不要背叛它
Never betray it.
魔鬼三角区
The Devil's Triangle.
他们船只的残骸
The last of their ships
就在我眼前灼灼燃烧
were burning before my eyes.
就在那胜利的一刻
And in that moment of victory...
我听见了那个声音
it's when I heard it.
嘿 这边 船长
Hey! Hold on, Capitán.
有艘船
One ship
想偷偷穿过迷雾里逃走
was trying to escape through the smoke.
今天是个航海的好日子 对吗
It's a lovely day for a sail, innit?
在那儿 那群乌鸦的巢穴里
And there, in the crow's nest...
还有一个年轻的海盗小子
there was this young pirate boy.
在我看来
The way I see it,
这里只剩下我们两个了
there's just the two of us left.
很简单 你现在向我投降 我也许能饶你一命
You surrender to me now and I'll let you live. Simple.
他站在那儿 就像个小鸟儿一样叽叽喳喳
He stood there looking like a little bird, eh?
所以从那天起
And from that day...
他赢得了一个称号 一直萦绕在我脑海里
he earned himself a name that would haunt me
缠扰着我接下来的每一天
for the rest of my days...
SSK字幕组
麻雀杰克
Jack the Sparrow.
SSK字幕组
很好 你现在向我投降 我就饶你不死
Right then. You surrender to me now and I let you live.
我应该会饶你不死吧
I shall let you live.
那小子在嘲笑我的能力 所以我朝他追去
This boy was mocking my power, so I chased him...
心想着我会用剑划开他的喉咙
knowing that I would run my knife along his neck...
而当他彻底死透之后
and when he was dead,
我将终于结束与海盗厮杀的日子
I would finish finally with the pirate's life.
追进去
Follow him in.
通知那些负责绞架的 抓一些绳索来
To the gallows. Grab some lines.
准备急转弯 向左舷转
Prepare the bootleg. Portside.
现在扔绳索
Throw it now.
开始转弯
Bootleg turn.
这是什么
What's all this?
给您的贡品 先生
Tribute, sir.
噢
Ooh!
他将我的一切都夺走了
He took everything from me...
我浑身灼烧着怒火
and filled me with rage.
和无尽的痛苦
And pain.
这就是故事的结尾了
And here is where the tale ends.
还没有到结尾 船长 看那里
Not yet, Capitán. There!
正如我承诺的那样 找到他了
Found as promised.
所以她说她拿到了地图
So she's saying she's got the map,
可她才是唯一能看懂地图的人吗
but she's the only one who can follow it?
那我们该不该杀死她
So we should shoot her?
别动她 她会带我们找到三叉戟的
Leave her be. She will take us to the Trident.
这话你已经呱呱呱地说了几个小时了
You've been saying that for hours.
我们至少确定两件事情 对吗
Two things we know are true, eh?
-没错 -第一件 白天里星星是不会亮起来的
- Yeah. - Stars don't shine by day.
第二件 她忘记带驴子了
And she forgot the donkey.
我们怎么才能到达一个不存在任何地图上的岛
How can we go to a spot where no land exists on any map?
这个天文钟走着一直是精准的伦敦时间
This chronometer keeps the exact time in London.
我一直用它来做海拔测量
I'm using it to make an altitude measurement
从而来决定刻度
to determine longitude.
只有这样我们才能在海上找到准确的位置
Only then will we find our exact spot at sea.
所以你指望靠着一块表来找到三叉戟吗
So you expect to find the Trident with a timepiece?
是的
Yes.
我的计算向来是精准无误的
My calculations are precise and true.
我不光是一个天文学家 还是个钟表学家
I'm not only an astronomer, I'm also a horologist.
唔
Mmm.
亲爱的 不需要为此感到羞耻
No shame in that, dear.
我是说 我们都得有个生计方式 对吧
I mean, we all have to earn a living, eh?
噢 当然了
Oh, yeah.
不 不 我是一个钟表学家
No. No, I'm a horologist.
我妈也是做婊的
So was my mum.
可她并没有像你自鸣得意地这么大声
But she didn't crow about it as loud as you.
你是说你母亲有学术上的才能吗
Are you saying your mother was academically inclined?
倒不如说 她更喜欢平躺任人上
More like, horizontally reclined.
钟表学是一门与时间有关的学问
Horology is the study of time.
没错 她也经常看着她的表 算时间到没到
And she was always looking at her watch.
我可以作证
I can vouch for that.
所以没有人能找到地图上的标记点 除了你 对吗
So no one can find the "X" But you, right?
-是的 -那驴子呢
-No. - And the donkey?
船尾方向有艘船
Ship to the aft!
萨拉查
Salazar.
杰克 那群死人们只有完成他们的复仇才会罢休的
Jack, the dead will not rest until they get their revenge.
死人们
Dead?
不 不 死人们从来不包括在我们和你们的交易当中
No, no. The dead were never part of this deal.
我们当初就不该跟着
We should have never followed
一个霉运连连的海盗 和一个女巫来出海
a luckless pirate and a witch to sea.
够了 就到这里了 杀了他们
Right, that's it. Kill 'em all.
杀了我 我就死了
Kill me and I'll be dead.
而其他那些死人们
And then the other dead
就不能够达成他们
won't be able to have their revenge...
对我的复仇了
against me.
毕竟我已经死了
Being dead.
你说什么
What?
而他死了会让他们更加愤怒 他说的没错
Which will anger them even more. He's right.
没错
That's right.
是不是所有海盗都这么蠢啊
Are all pirates this stupid?
没错
Yes.
-嗯 -有道理
- Yeah. - Yeah.
那我们该怎么办
What are we going to do?
作为船长 我能否建议
As Captain, might I suggest...
反抗啊 你一定得建议他们反抗吗
Mutiny? You had to suggest a mutiny?
卡瑞娜 死人们就要来了
Carina, the dead are coming.
可惜我选择不去相信那些超自然的鬼话
Well, I choose not to believe in supernatural nonsense.
你难道没有看到我们身后跟着的船吗
Do you not see what's behind us?
放它们下去 放下去
Drop them. Drop them.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
那艘船上的人们在找杰克
The men on that ship are looking for Jack
而杰克是在这艘小舟上
and Jack is on this boat.
所以我决定游过去
So I'm going to swim for it.
你怎么敢做这种如果我是你我也会做的事
How dare you do exactly what I would do if I were you.
-卡瑞娜 快停下 -别 别 别 不要停 继续脱
- Carina, stop that. - No, no, no. Don't stop that.
我们已经划了这么远了
This has gone far enough.
不 并没有
No, it has not.
别听这小子的 继续脱 继续脱
Listen not to him. Carry on. Carry on.
为什么 她都差不多脱光了啊
Why? She was almost finished.
我看到她的脚踝了
I saw her ankles.
如果你这家伙能管住你那大嘴巴
You'd have seen a lot more
你本可以看到更多部位的 蠢货
if you'd have kept your cake hole shut.
杀了斯派洛
Kill the Sparrow.
噢 这不是好事 对吗
Oh, that's not good, is it?
继续划 小伙子 划快点 划快点
Keep rowing, man. Faster. Faster.
不 我不干了
No. That's it.
我要跟她一起游过去
I'm going with her.
你竟然为了一个只穿着女性内裤的钟表学家而抛弃我吗
You would leave me for some horologist in her knickers?
是的
Yes.
你们男人没一个好东西
You men are all alike.
鲨鱼啊
Shark.
亨利
Henry!
看样子根本不管用啊
Doesn't seem to be working!
不 我们会没事的 我们会没事的
No, we'll be fine. We'll be fine.
前进
Vamos!
他们是怎么做到的
How do they do that?
我们得游到岸上了 我来分散鲨鱼们的注意力
We have to swim for it. I'll distract them.
就是现在
Now!
噢 该死
Oh, shoo!
快走开啦
Go away!
亨利
Henry!
噢
Oh!
嗨 杰克·斯派洛
Hi, Jack Sparrow.
麻雀杰克
Jack the Sparrow.
你是西班牙人吗
You're Spanish?
天啊 你们都是鬼魂
You're ghosts!
噢
Oh.
他们竟然走不到陆地上
They're unable to step on land.
虽然我早就知道了
I knew that, though.
天啊 有鬼啊
Ghosts!
卡瑞娜
Carina!
你很快就要为你所做的一切付出代价了
You will soon pay for what you did to me.
不 不 不 实在没必要麻烦你们了 真的
No, no, no. There's no need to bother, really.
-卡瑞娜 -我没时间和你们唠家常了
- Carina! - I have no time to chat...
因为我的地图刚刚尖叫着跑走了
because me map's just run away.
我会这里等着你的
I will be waiting for you!
你为什么要等着我哟
Why would you be waiting for me?
他为什么要等着我 好可怕
Why would he be waiting for me?
海盗们
Pirates!
斯库朗
Scrum.
船长
Captain.
杰克经常告诉我
Jack always told me that
如果他发生了什么不测
if anything should ever happen to him...
他希望你能来当船长
he wanted you to be captain.
真好 可是大家伙都投票选了你啊
Yeah, but the men voted for you.
所以你才会带上船长帽子啊
That's why you got a captain's hat.
虽然话是这么说
Be that as it may...
他的愿望不能违背
them were his wishes,
所以当个好小伙 接管船舵吧
so be a good lad and take the wheel.
以及 呃 你
And, uh, you...
带好这顶船长帽子
take the captain's hat.
噢
Oh.
这真的是我最自豪的时刻了 我长这么
This is the proudest moment of my...
我们会把你们的船长活活打死
We will beat your captain to death...
除非他说出杰克那帮人到底去了那儿
until he reveals where they're heading.
卡琳娜
Carina!
我知道你在苦恼什么 小伙子
I know what's ailing you, boy.
你很痒 却又挠不到
You've got the unscratchable itch.
卡琳娜是唯一一个
Carina is the only one
能帮我们找到三叉戟的人
who can help us find the Trident...
我不爱她
and I'm not in love with her.
爱
Love?
有人说了爱这个字吗  你在说什么
Who said anything about love? What are you talking about?
挠不到的痒
The unscratchable itch?
疥疮 我指的是疥疮
Scabies. I'm talking about scabies.
小小的螨虫钻到皮肤下面
Small mites that burrow under the skin.
我确实为此苦恼 好多年了
It's certainly ailing me, has been for years.
噢 不会吧
Oh, no.
汉格曼湾
陌生者勿入
救命
Help!
救救我
Help me!
- 卡琳娜 - 救命
- Carina! - Help!
- 亨利 救我 - 救救她
- Henry, help me! - Help her!
根据王法
By rule of the King,
我判你们所有人死刑
I sentence you all to death!
我认为 我们应该告诉对方
I think we should tell each other
各自埋藏宝藏的地方
where our treasures are buried...
万一谁活了下来
just in case one of us survives.
噢 好主意
Oh, good idea.
你先说吧
You go first.
我把宝藏埋在阿鲁巴两棵交叉生长的棕榈树
My treasure is buried between two crossed palm trees...
中间的无名冢下 你的呢
in an unmarked grave in Aruba. What about yours?
我没有宝藏
I haven't got any.
你答应要带杰克过来的
You promised me Jack's blood!
但杰克被抓了
CAPTAIN BARBOSSA: But Jack be trapped!
他逃不出那座岛
He can never escape that island.
他在陆地上
He's on land!
哈喽
Hello.
我赞成我们的交易  我和我的人会去岸上
I upheld our deal. Me men and meself will go ashore.
把那个卑鄙的背信者带给你
The scurvy traitor will be yours...
以我的名誉担保
on me honour.
名誉  就你这样还谈名誉 什么名誉
Honour? What honour, hombre? What honour?
你都不知道什么是名誉
You don't know what honour is.
放我一条生路
Spare me my life,
我能帮你捉到那个小矮子
and I'll fetch you the Sparrow.
您看行吗
An accord?
醒醒 斯派洛
Wake up, Sparrow.
醒醒 斯派洛 还债的时候到了
Wake up, Sparrow. It's time to pay your debt.
皮格 皮格·凯丽
Pig... Pig Kelly?
老朋友
Me old mate.
朋友 你们听到了吗  小伙子们
Mate? You hear that, boys?
这个海盗骗走了我一大堆银子
This lyin' pirate owes me a plunder of silver...
老天有眼 让他来到汉格曼湾
and luck has brought him to Hangman's Bay...
立马受到应得的惩罚
where he can settle his debt here and now.
噢 我会的 我会的 皮格
Oh, and I will. I will, Pig.
你说个价钱
Name your price.
她叫贝翠诗
Her name is Beatrice...
我可怜的寡妇妹妹
and she's my poor, widowed sister.
那是什么
What is that?
她在找个值得敬仰的男人
She's been looking for a respectable man.
那就是你
But you'll have to do.
路易斯 我们开始吧
Louis, let's get on with this.
不 为什么 为什么我们要这样
No! Why? Why would we do that?
让她成为真正的女人吧 杰克
To make an honest woman of her, Jack.
祝贺你 今天是你的大喜之日
Congratulations. It's your wedding day.
我们开始吧
Let us begin.
我们会在马厮度蜜月
We'll honeymoon in the barn.
不 不要 不要
No, no, no.
现在 皮格 我怎么能
Now, Pig, how could I...
真正地让一个本就是女人的人变成女人呢
honestly make an honest woman out of it?
那个 她 我的意思是 她
That... Her. I mean, her.
这是些什么东东
What are those things?
我们的孩子
Our children.
最好不要直视他们的眼睛
Best not look them in the eye.
把最好的伴郎和伴娘带来
Bring the best man and the bridesmaid.
我直视他们的眼睛了
I looked it in the eye.
请把手放在《圣经》上
Place your hand on the Bible.
我有疥疮
I've got scabies.
- 我也是 - 呃
- So do I. - JACK SPARROW: Ugh!
把手放到《圣经》上来
Place your hand on the Bible.
我尿床
I'm a bed-wetter.
说 我愿意
Say "I do..."
不然我就打穿你的头
or I'll put a bullet in your skull.
杰克 他们想杀了我们
Jack, they're going to kill us!
- 我不在乎 -快说我愿意
- I don't care! - Just say "I do."
- 最后一次机会 杰克 - 等等
- Last chance, Jack. - Wait!
想必 这不合法度
Surely, this is not legal.
这不合法
This is not legal.
他说得对
He's right.
有人反对这场婚礼吗
Does any man here object to these nuptials?
- 我愿意 - 恭喜你
- I do. - Congratulations!
你可以亲吻新娘了
You may kiss the bride!
不
No.
你喜欢海鲜 对吗
You like seafood, do you?
- 快点
- Come on!
杰克 我们又见面了
Jack, we meet again.
西克特
JACK SPARROW: Hector!
他是我在这世界最好的朋友
This is me bestest mate in the whole world.
我总是偶然知道你的行踪
I always knew you'd settle down eventually.
你给我带了礼物吗
Did you bring me a gift?
我会的
That'll do.
你看起来特别棒
You look marvellous.
脚上好像被捆了很多下
Got quite the spring in your step.
你的腿长回来了吗
Has your leg grown back?
呃 船长 我们是不是该回萨拉查
Uh, Captain, shouldn't we be getting back to Salazar...
用斯派洛先生的命来换我们的命
trade Mr Sparrow's life in for our own?
- 不错 那我们就能
CAPTAIN BARBOSSA: Aye, that we could...
但我是为了波塞冬的三叉戟来的
but I've come for the Trident of Poseidon.
你准备出卖那个死人吗
You're gonna double-cross the dead?
你承诺过的
You did promise.
用它 我可以让那个夺走我的海洋管理权的死人
And with it, I'll gut the dead that stole
开膛破肚
my command of the sea.
我特别喜欢这个计划
As much as I love this plan...
没有什么能跑得过他那艘破船
no vessel can outrun that wretched hull of a ship.
但有一条船 杰克
But there be one, Jack.
是我所知速度最快的 那就是 黑珍珠号
The fastest ship I know, the Pearl...
五年前 它被黑胡子困在瓶子里
trapped in that bottle by Blackbeard five winters ago.
用那个恶棍
By the power of that
独有的力量
blackguard's sovereign blade...
在此 我将让黑珍珠号
I hereby release the Black Pearl
重焕荣光
to her former and rightful glory.
准备好
Get ready!
准备好吧
Get ready for it!
它来了
It's coming!
它来了 它来了 它来了
It's coming! It's coming, it's coming!
靠边站 靠边站
Stand aside! Stand aside!
它来了
It's coming!
它缩小了
It's shrunken.
为什么它会缩小
Why doesn't it unshrink?
也许太冷了
Maybe it's cold, huh?
她需要到海里去
She needs the sea.
她曾是艘好船
She was a fine ship.
- 让
- Let...
只有一人能当船长
There be room for only one captain.
噢
JACK SPARROW: Ooh!
肮脏的野兽
Filthy beast.
是时候和死人交锋了
Time to race the dead.
只有陆地是安全的
JACK SPARROW: The only safe place is the land.
为什么我们要离开陆地
Why are we going away from the land? Anyone?
船长 你的地图不完整
Captain, your map is incomplete.
我可以带大家到翠登特如果你不相信我的话
I can take us to the Trident if you'd only trust me.
有人吗
JACK SPARROW: Anyone?
你听到我说的话了吗
Did you not hear anything I just said?
你是说那颗星
So you be saying that that star
假装是张地图
is pretendin' to be a map?
先生 没有一张地图里有岛
Sir, there is no island on any map
和那位女士说的不一样
to support what the woman says.
船长 你不需要理解她
Captain, you don't have to understand her.
信她就好了
Just believe her.
有人吗
Anyone?
如果有尖的东西 我就能撬开那个锁
If we had something sharp, I could pick that lock.
你没法在这儿找到尖东西
You're not gonna find anything sharp in here.
别动 臭老鼠
Keep still, you bilge rat.
船长
Captain!
请别这么叫 我不想再当船长了
No, please! I don't wanna be captain any more!
放了他们
Release 'em!
先生 你该不会让
Sir, you wouldn't allow...
一个女人来开你的船吧
a woman to steer your ship?
她可以跟着她的星星 不然我们都会死
She will follow her star, or we'll all die together.
黑珍珠号 她回归啦
The Black Pearl! She sails again!
加油 伙计们
Come on, lads!
这艘船 这些鬼魂
This ship, those ghosts...
根本就不符合逻辑
There can be no logical explanation.
海洋传说都是真的 卡琳娜
The myths of the sea are real, Carina.
很高兴你终于知道自己错了
I'm glad you can finally see you were wrong.
错了
Wrong?
我或许只是有点疑惑
Perhaps I had some doubts.
这是我听过的最烂的道歉了
This is the worst apology I've ever heard.
道歉 为什么我要道歉
Apology? Why would I apologise?
因为我们被死人追杀
Because we've been chased by the dead,
搭乘一条从瓶子里拿出来的船航行
sailing on a ship raised from a bottle.
你的那套科学论能解释吗
Where is your science in that?
好吧 那我道歉就是了
Fine, then I will apologise.
继续说
Go on, then.
尽管 有人认为你欠我个道歉
Although one could argue that you owe me an apology...
例如我的生命正遭受到海盗和死人的威胁
as my life has been threatened by pirates and dead men.
你现在也是相信的 遗憾地说
Which you now believe in, sorry to say.
道歉我接受了
Apology accepted.
我去眺望台
I'm going to the lookout.
很高兴你能跟我看得一样
I'm glad you see it my way.
十二度到港===
Twelve degrees to port!
- 准备好枪 - 好的
- Ready the guns. - Aye!
备好枪
Ready the guns!
这些海盗是往翠登特去的
Those pirates are going for the Trident.
你是从哪儿看出来的 姑娘
Where did you get that from, missy?
我知道这本书
I know this book.
多年前从一条意大利船偷来的
Stolen from an Italian ship many years ago.
偷 你搞错了吧
Stolen? No, you're mistaken.
封页上有一颗红宝石 我可忘不了它
There was a ruby on the cover I would not soon forget.
这是我父亲给我的
This was given to me by my father...
他是个十分相信科学的人
who was clearly a man of science.
他很明显是个惯犯
He was clearly a common thief.
我父亲带给我的回忆不荣你这个海盗
The memory of my father will not be defiled
的烂醉玷污
by the tongue of a pirate.
这本日记是我出生就有的
This diary is my birthright.
父亲把它放在孤儿院的台阶上
Left to me on the steps of a children's home.
连带着名字和一些其他物品
Along with a name and nothing else.
噢 所以你是孤儿咯
Oh, so you're an orphan.
你叫什么
What be you called?
北边最美的星就是我的名字
Brightest star in the North gave me my name.
那便是卡琳娜
That would be Carina.
卡琳娜·斯密斯
Carina Smyth.
所以你才知道你的星星
So you do know your stars.
我是个船长
I'm a captain.
我知道跟着哪颗星才能回家
I know which stars to follow home.
斯密斯
JACK SPARROW: Smyth.
这不是个寻常的姓
Smyth is quite an unusual name.
我们以前是不是
Did we not once...
也认识一个史密斯
know someone called Smyth?
别想套我的话
Shut your trap.
她叫什么来着
What was her name?
就在我嘴边儿 哦
It's right on the tip of me tongue. Oh!
舌头你还想要吗
Do you wanna lose that tongue?
玛格丽特·史密斯
Margaret Smyth.
啊
Aye.
不如我们做个交易好了
Should we make an accord then?
还是让我告诉那个人真相？
Or shall I tell you-know-who what we both know to be true?
到死都别说
We both take this secret to our graves.
看来我猜的没错 我不过是随口一说
You mean, it is true? I was bluffing.
我是认真的
I'm not.
杀了我 在亡灵海盗面前你就失去了筹码
You kill me, you got nothing to bargain the dead with.
所以你得留我一命
So you need me.
赫克托 我有句话一定要讲
I'll have to be frank, Hector.
你这么丑
You are very, very ugly.
怎么能生出这么
So how could you produce
漂亮的女儿呢
a fetching creature such as that?
玛格丽特死了
Margaret died.
我虽然没什么成就
I summoned as much honour
但孩子是我最大的荣耀
as a worthless blaggard ever could.
我把孩子留在孤儿院
I placed the infant in an orphanage...
从没去看过她
never to see her again.
我留给她一颗红宝石
I thought the ruby might afford her
是想她能过得轻松一些
some ease in life...
我从没想过她靠的却是那些胡乱的涂鸦
but I never imagined she'd take those scribblings...
还学有所成
and make a life of her own.
而她的知识又促使了我们的重逢
A life that's led her back to me.
我怎么觉得这剧情走向
I'd say this puts me
对我十分有利啊 好爸爸
in a rather favourable position, Daddy.
有话直说
You tell me what you want.
我要我的罗盘
I want me compass.
216桶好酒
216 barrels of rum.
以及这只小可爱
And the monkey.
你想要杰克（猴子）
You want Jack?
是吃 我想以它作为我的晚餐
Dinner. I want to eat him, I want to eat that monkey...
不可能 杰克
No deal, Jack.
像她那样罕见的聪慧少女
A clever young woman such as that would never believe...
是不会相信我这样的人会是她爹的
that a swine like me could ever be her blood.
而且 三叉戟一定会是我的
And the Trident will be mine.
海军
Redcoats!
海军来了
点火准备
Prepare to fire!
拿起武器
Man that gun!
他们的船从右舷方向来
She comes starboard.
我们要战斗到底
We shall fight to the last.
黑珍珠号决不能在落入他人之手
The Pearl will not be taken from me again.
长官
Sir.
海上的控制权
Only the British Empire
只能属于我们大英帝国
will hold to the power of the sea.
不管发生了什么 专心开船
Whatever happens, stay your course.
杰克·斯派洛
Jack Sparrow!
Jack Sparrow.
我找你讨债来了
I've come with a butcher's bill.
他在哪儿
Where is he?
为自己而战 至死方休
Defend yourselves, men. To the death!
快点儿啊你
Hurry up, man.
你是拿黄油润的刀吗？请问？
What did you sharpen it with? Butter?
看你往哪儿躲
There's nowhere to hide.
勇敢地战斗 保卫黑珍珠
Let's be brave. Save the Pearl!
应该就是它了
This has to be it.
应该就是这儿了
It has to be here.
快找到那片陆地
Find that land.
要不然我们都是死路一条
Or we'll all die.
就快到了
We're nearly there!
就在这附近
It's here somewhere.
哦
Oh!
嗷
Ow.
哈
Ha!
哇哦
Whoa...
小姐 你找到那个地方了吗
Have you found what you're looking for yet, miss?
快了快了
I'm trying!
星星就快消失了
The stars will soon be gone.
哇哦 哇哦
Whoa! Whoa!
卡琳娜
Carina!
亨利 快看
Henry, look!
就是那座岛
The island is there.
你成功了
You found it!
那座岛
The island.
陆地
Land.
快回玛丽号
Get to the Mary!
卡琳娜
Carina!
亨利
Henry!
他们把亨利抓走了
They took Henry!
现在只有三叉戟能救他了
The Trident be all that can save him now.
我们必须找到它
Then we have to find it.
它到底在哪儿
Where is it?
应该就在这儿啊
It has to be here.
杰克 看啊
Look at it, Jack.
这是我见过的最美丽的景色
It's the most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
这就是我父亲希望我找到的东西
This is what my father wanted me to find.
一堆礁石
The rocks?
不 不是这个
No, not rocks.
是星星
Stars.
这就是号称天书的地图
This is The Map No Man Can Read.
这座岛正是星图的倒影
This island is a perfect reflection of the heavens.
有颗星星不见了
One star's missing.
快
Quickly!
我们必须要找到三叉戟救回亨利
We have to find the Trident to save Henry.
赫克托 我觉得你应该知道
Hector, I think you should know,
她是一个钟表学家
she's a horologist.
它为什么不亮了
Why isn't it glowing?
卡琳娜 拼上去吧
Finish it, Carina.
遗落的星星
The missing star.
为了我的父亲
For my father.
对
Aye.
为了他
Do it for him.
看
Look.
波塞冬的墓穴
Poseidon's tomb.
这边
This way.
船长 你知道那有多危险
Capitán, you know the danger.
别去了
Don't do it.
他别无选择
He has no choice.
杰克在陆地上找寻着三叉戟
Jack is on land going for the Trident.
船长 肯定还有别的办法
Capitán, there must be another way.
你一旦附身于活体之中 就没有回头路了
Once you possess the living, there's no coming back.
你会永远被困在他的身体里
You will be trapped in his body forever.
只要拿到三叉戟一切都不是问题
The Trident will set me free.
是该杀死斯派洛了
Time to kill a Sparrow.
不
No!
杰克 看 那儿
Look, Jack. There it is.
三叉戟
The Trident.
杰克 -嗯
Jack! - Huh?
嗯
Huh?
杰克 伤了我就是伤了这小子
You cut me, you cut the boy, Jack.
亨利
Henry!
你好啊 斯派洛
Hola, Sparrow.
哦 不好
Oh, no.
我讨厌斯派洛 去死吧
I hate the Sparrow. Die, Sparrow.
亨利
Henry!
他能在陆地上行走了 快醒醒
He's walking on land. Please.
亨利 醒醒
Henry, wake up.
哦 滚开
Oh, piss off!
哇哦
Whoa!
亨利 醒醒 他要杀了杰克
Henry, wake up. He's killing Jack.
亨利
Henry!
海之神力
Power of the sea.
什么
What?
海之神力
The power of the sea.
要释放海之神力
"To release the power of the sea...
必须分离一切
"All must divide."
如果说海之神力全都存于三叉戟的话 那么
If the Trident holds all the power, then...
每个诅咒也是藏于其中的
Then every curse is held inside.
我还是那句话
As I told you before...
只要你投降 我就会饶你
surrender to me now and I'll let you...
一命
live.
要我投降
You want me to surrender?
万一呢
Maybe.
今天就是你的死期
This is where the tale ends.
不
No!
嘘
Shh.
分离
Divide.
亨利
Henry!
分离 断开
Divide. Break.
砍断三叉戟 就能
Break the Trident and you'll...
解除海上的一切诅咒
Break every curse at sea.
一切诅咒都被解除了
All curses are broken.
我们不再是行尸走肉了
We are flesh and blood!
黑珍珠号
The Pearl!
我的黑珍珠号
My Pearl!
爬上去
Climb!
跑 快
Move! Fast!
抓稳了 孩子们
Hold it steady, boys!
别让绳子滑动了
Don't let her slip!
杰克
Jack!
跳
Jump!
快点儿
Faster!
锚 拉上来
Up! Anchor!
快把锚拉上来
Get the anchor up! Quick!
停 停 拉上来
Stop! Stop! Bring it up!
往上拉 往上拉 快
Bring it up! Bring it up! Come on!
往上拉
Bring it up!
船长
Capitán!
哦 断了
Oh, crumbs!
哇哦 哇哦
Whoa. Whoa.
哦
Oh!
我抓住你了
I've got you!
使劲儿
Stronger.
我是你的什么
Who am I to you?
珍宝
Treasure.
抓紧了
Hold on!
赫克托
Hector!
抓住她的右舷
Hold her starboard!
赫克托 作为海盗的一生
Pirate's life, Hector.
你还好吗
You all right?
我也不知道
I don't know.
亨利 有一瞬间 我以为我拥有了全世界
For a moment, I had everything, Henry.
然而现在 一切又荡然无存了
Now, it's all gone again.
史密斯小姐 还没有呢
It's not all gone, Ms Smyth.
巴波萨
Barbossa.
叫我巴波萨
My name is Barbossa.
杰克还真说对了
Maybe Jack was right.
他说什么了
About what?
我内心深处的躁动
The unscratchable itch.
你这是干嘛
What did you do that for?
确定一下是不是真的你
Just checking it's truly you.
万一又被鬼魂附身了呢
That you're not still a ghost.
是我
It's me.
那就是
Then I was...
你的错
Wrong.
很小的失误 虽然
Slightly in error. Although...
原谅你了
Apology accepted.
荷兰人号
The Dutchman.
SSK字幕组
亨利
Henry.
是的 父亲
Yes, Father.
孩子 让我好好看看你
Let me look at you, son.
你怎么做到的
How did you do it?
怎么解除诅咒的
How did you break the curse?
听我给你讲一个传奇
Let me tell you a tale.
关于人类历史上最为伟大的宝藏
A tale of the greatest treasure known to man.
快讲给我听听
That's a tale I wanna hear.
秀恩爱死的快
What a truly revolting sight.
开道
Make way!
杰克·斯派洛在甲板上了
Captain Jack Sparrow on deck!
是的
Indeed!
船长 欢迎回来
Welcome back, Captain.
哦 谢谢大家 借过
Oh, thank you very much. Coming through.
船长
Captain!
谢谢
Thank you.
我记得你哦
I remember you.
先生们 感谢大家
Sirs. Thank you.
哦 太好了 吉布斯总管
Oh, good. Master Gibbs.
船长 船由您掌舵
The ship is yours, Captain.
啊 谢谢
Ah, thank you.
小可爱
Monkey.
谢谢
Thank you.
船长 下一站去哪儿呢
What be our heading, Captain?
吉布斯总管 我们跟随星星前进吧
We shall follow the stars, Master Gibbs.
好的 好的 船长
Aye, aye, Captain!
我要去遥远的天边 赴一场浪漫的约会
I have a rendezvous beyond my beloved horizon.
翻译 Jennifer
翻译 默默吼
翻译 penguinnknk
翻译 小葵
翻译 方黑羊
翻译 Crescendo
翻译 何旋木
校对 Bezero
特效 阿桑奇
特效 阿黎
压制 hhjie
总监  王祖贤老婆